I think I started to suspect
it was a bad movie
when I looked at the script
and saw the title,
Serial Ape-ist 2:
Monkey See, Monkey Kill.
Uh, spoiler alert:
(Wil:)after the monkey sees, it kills.
(Leonard:)Psst.
(Wil:)I've just been handed a note.
(Wil:)I'm going to read it.
"Wil, do you want
more Diet Coke?
Also, we have juice."
I-I didn't want to interrupt.
(Wil:)Uh, that voice you just heard
(Wil:)belongs to Leonard,
Penny's fiancé.
(Wil:)Uh, Leonard, why don't you grab
some headphones and join us?
(Leonard:)Really?
Yeah.
(chuckles) Yeah, great.
(Wil:)So, while Leonard
gets set up,
(Wil:)let's take a call.
(Wil:)Hello, caller, you are on
(Wil:)with Penny and Wil
from Serial Ape-ist 2.
WOMAN:
I don't have a question.
(Caller:)I just want to say
I'm a big fan of the movie.
(Caller:)I've seen it, like, ten times.
(Penny:)Okay, well, I'll apologize
for the first time,